dealaboo.com 2013-08-06

# Privacy Policy | Dealaboo

We reserve the right to revise this privacy policy as and when necessary, users are advised to periodically review the privacy policy.

The information collected from the users includes personal information as well as non-personal information.

##  Personal Information

The personal information that we collect includes the user’s email address, location including city & country and deal preferences. We use the information to send our users deal newsletters based on their interest and preferences. If a user do not want to receive newsletter, he or she can unsubscribe at anytime. We do not sell or rent your personal information to any third party. The only reason to collect your personal information is to send best deals of your interest right in your inbox. 

##  Non-personal Information

This includes the addresses (URL) of the websites visited before and after visiting our website, your IP address, your browser information, etc. Your non-personal information may be shared with the merchants at Dealaboo for order processing activities, etc. We do not take responsibility of merchants’ activities and their direct communication with you. In addition to the merchants on our website, we may also share your information with third parties for activities related to your purchases and payments.

##  The Purpose of Collecting User Information

This information is collected for a number of reasons including, but not limited to, keeping the users updated about our services/products, analysis of website usage, improvement of the website performance, etc. Other reasons for collecting your personal and non-personal information are: analysis of the demographics of the users of the website, to maintain constant communication with the users, helping law enforcement agencies with any investigations, etc.

**Information Security**

Security of the personal information of our users is one of our top priorities. All of the critical data including users’ personal information is safely kept on secure servers which are accessible to only select authorized personnel. We use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) to encrypt sensitive information. While we make every possible effort to ensure the security of your data, we do not guarantee its security nor do we take responsibility for any loss or misuse of the information during transmission to and from our website. Because the information we save is limited to user email addresses, their location and browsing behavior - nothing more.

##  Information Disclosure

Your non-personal information may be revealed to our partners, advertisers and other such parties. While you visit our website, this information may be used by third-party advertisers to serve you with advertisements about products/services that may be of interest to you.

##  Use of ‘Cookies’

To improve your interaction with our website and to make it more personalized, we use ‘cookies’ ( _a small text file created by an Internet site which is placed on a visitors PC. It only identifies the computer used by an individual_ ) to store relevant information on your computer. This information helps us recognize you every time you visit our website. We customize your interaction with our website by using the information stored through the ‘cookies’. In addition to the cookies we store on your computer, third-party advertisers may also store cookies on your computer while serving advertisements and marketing messages. The cookies stored by the third-party advertisers are beyond our control and are not covered by the terms of this privacy policy.

Our services/products are not designed for use by minors; therefore, we do not intentionally collect personal information from individuals under 18 years of age.

Certain areas of our website may allow posting of user generated content. These areas include our blog and discussion boards.

This Privacy Policy is applicable only to the information collected on Dealaboo. The collection and dissemination of information on third-party websites and other websites linking to our website are governed by separate privacy policies on those websites. You should review the policy on such websites before using them.
